Music
Thank you for watching!
Go to.
Ai, Rico, everyone, Sakura, Ryu, and Miyu.
This is our stage from here.
Place time.
Let's have fun.
Ride, ride, ride.
Music.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching
Let's talk about it.
Yeah.
Where are you, Kigo-San, Kigo-Ne-
Where are you, Kigo?
Where's Osakata, Kigo-San, Kigo-Ne-
I don't know, I don't know, Spider with my lips
I love Atagata, I love Atagata, I love Atagata, I love Atagata, I love Atagata
I heard that FUNZOKIN-san is also here in Oita, so
Dagata dokosa can't be left out, right?
Yes, that's right.
From the very beginning.
First things first.
And the costumes.
And this.
Dagatadokosa.
I wanted to do a song called “Student.
I wanted to include a song with a big theme, but...
But we just...
We didn't have enough time.
You know?
That's too bad. Shame.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Our recent songs are more like dance music.
but we also have songs with a ska-core band sound.
When I saw the performers this time
I thought it would be a good set up to have both of them.
There was also a corner where we swung to guts rock.
There was a sense of nostalgia.
I hope it will continue in the future.
There was a lot of enthusiasm.
I wondered if it was a hot spring.
The audience was really enthusiastic.
And even people who didn't know us waved to us.
There were two stages and I could see people dancing on the other side of the stage.
It was a live concert where everyone really became one.
I was so happy.
The audience was really excited.
I think it was because we were able to play a lot of songs that were easy to imitate free style.
I think it was also because we played a lot of songs that were easy to imitate free improvisation.
That's how you have fun, isn't it?
I think there was a sense that many people were having fun together.
Also, when Dendera Leuver was played...
I don't know what it is, but there were a lot of people who were playing with their hands
I don't know what it was, but there was an increase in the number of people who were playing with their hands.
That's for sure.
They tried their best to imitate me.
You were doing your best.
I felt like I wanted to teach him.
In my case, I usually don't do it by myself.
I usually don't come across new music unless I try to listen to his music.
It's hard for me to find new music unless I try to listen to his music.
But with me, it's like...
Since I came all the way here
I'd like to see the various artists who perform at the show.
I'm sure the artists I see at the show are really cool, so
I'm able to listen to more music.
I really like the feeling of expanding my taste.
This time, I'm going to show you You'll show me this time.
Yes, I've pretty much been an angel myself since I joined the stage.
I've been able to experience a festival for the first time.
There's a lot of new music that I've encountered.
I've been able to learn from them.
There's a lot to learn from them.
I think the best thing is to have fun.
I think that's what I like about festivals.
Of course the live music is exciting, but the local food and stalls are also great.
but also the local food and the stalls.
I feel like the whole community comes together to make the festival a success.
I feel like the whole community comes together to make the festival more exciting.
I feel like I want to be a part of it.
Yeah.
I like the fun atmosphere of the festival, the live music, and the fun that happens every day.
Aaron
Tension style, Don!
Thanks for your time.
It's diagonal.
No, no, no.
Too difficult.
Here we go.
That's it.
You've done a great job.
Really?
It looks so big!
Ruth has a small view.
Cute!
ón
Ducky.
That bereaved laugh.
Thanks for watching!
The set-lift of the live show had a lot of intense songs, but I'm happy.
It's the best.
I'll get right in right away.
I understand.
There were people watching while getting in during the live show, and I was jealous. I was envious of the people who were watching the show while entering the room during the concert.
I thought it was such a luxury, so I joined in at the end of the show.
The weather was so nice!
I'm so glad!
Is it supposed to be sunny tomorrow?
No, it's supposed to be rainy or cloudy or rainy.
It was cloudy and rainy.
But I'm sure it's going to be fine.
It's going to be fine.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to...
Chidokin and...
Basho.
What's that?
It's like a goody bag.
I'm going to the “yes” booth.
If it's your partner.
It's your partner.
But, um, you and your partner...
They're going to deliver pink ale from home
They seem to be delivering it to me.
I'll take that power and do my best.
Every time I get asked to be a screen car, do you think I'll become a screen car?
I'll be a screen car!
Thank you very much. One more thing, please.
Thank you very much.
This way, please.
It was a lot of fun.
Wow, good!
Thank you very much.
And for the money.
For the money.
And the money.
Seriously?
I had so much fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Cheers.
It was delicious.
Cheers!
Thank you very much.
Gigolok, our stage is over, and we've had a bit of fun.
We had a lot of fun. Of course, there are many more to come, but once there, we were able to visit many places and have fun.
First of all, our stage, how did we do?
There were so many people who came to see us, and even people who had never seen the Batten Show before danced with us,
And the members of the group also got really excited, which made us very happy.
We were wearing ear monitors, but you could hear us so well.
Thanks to everyone's enthusiasm, we felt we had to respond to them, and we were able to give a passionate performance. Thank you very much.
But the stage was so big,
I honestly didn't know that there were venues and parks where festivals could be held,
So we were very happy that a big festival was held here in Kyushu and that we were able to perform.
There was a lot of delicious food, and there were footbaths, too.
And there are no footbaths either.
So I thought it was great that we could enjoy both the festival, the music, and the charm of Oita.
It's great.
And this one, too.
There was even a live comedy show.
Enjoy yourself.
I had a lot of fun.
I was very happy to see that.
Yes, I hope that we will be able to hold more festivals like this in the future, even on our own initiative,
I hope that we will be able to hold such festivals in the future, even on our own initiative,
I hope that we can continue to do more activities that are rooted in Kyushu in the future.
I will do my best so that more and more people will know about us.
I will do my best.
Seino.
Gigolok.